<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Amazon SageMaker Workshop on Amazon RoboMaker Workshop</title>
    <link>/workshop/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Amazon SageMaker Workshop on Amazon RoboMaker Workshop</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/workshop/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How Amazon SageMaker Autopilot works</title>
      <link>/workshop/howitworks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/workshop/howitworks/</guid>
      <description>Using a single API call, or a few clicks in Amazon SageMaker Studio, SageMaker Autopilot first inspects your data set, and runs a number of candidates to figure out the optimal combination of data preprocessing steps, machine learning algorithms and hyperparameters. Then, it uses this combination to train an Inference Pipeline, which you can easily deploy either on a real-time endpoint or for batch processing. As usual with Amazon SageMaker, all of this takes place on fully-managed infrastructure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started</title>
      <link>/workshop/getstarted/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/workshop/getstarted/</guid>
      <description>Getting Started To get started, you will need an AWS account. You can either use:
 Your own account; or &amp;hellip; An account provided through Event Engine, as part of an AWS organized workshop   If you are running this workshop as part of an Event Engine lab, please log into the console using this link and enter your hash.
 Otherwise, if you are doing this lab on your own, please follow the following instructions to either:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Load Autopilot Example</title>
      <link>/workshop/loadexample/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/workshop/loadexample/</guid>
      <description>Load AutoPilot Example Load Example on Sagemaker Studio   Navigate to the Commands tab - 4th icon on the left (   ) and click &amp;ldquo;Getting Started&amp;rdquo;.   Then click &amp;ldquo;Create Autopilot Experiment&amp;rdquo; - you will see the following window:
    For Experiment name, enter : Sagemaker-test-autopilot&amp;rdquo; or something similar
  For S3 location of input data, enter : https://sagemaker-getting-started-data.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/bank-additional-full.csv
  For Target attribute name, enter : y</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Run Autopilot Example</title>
      <link>/workshop/runexample/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/workshop/runexample/</guid>
      <description>Run AutoPilot Example A typical introductory task in machine learning (the &amp;ldquo;Hello World&amp;rdquo; equivalent) is one that uses a dataset to predict whether a customer will enroll for a term deposit at a bank, after one or more phone calls. For more information about the task and the dataset used, see Bank Marketing Data Set.
Direct marketing, through mail, email, phone, etc., is a common tactic to acquire customers. Because resources and a customer&amp;rsquo;s attention are limited, the goal is to only target the subset of prospects who are likely to engage with a specific offer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workshop Clean-up</title>
      <link>/workshop/cleanup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/workshop/cleanup/</guid>
      <description>Workshop cleanup Please follow the steps below to shutdown or delete resources so you will not be charged.
  Delete the S3 bucket by selecting the bucket then clicking Delete from above the list of buckets.
  Delete any notebook instances you may have created.
  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>